The untold story of 007!
Everything or Nothing is a documentary film directed by Stevan Riley.
The story of three men with a shared dream: James
Bond franchise producers Albert R.
Broccoli and Harry Saltzman, and Bond creator and author Ian Fleming.
It’s the thrilling and inspiring narrative behind the longest running
film franchise in cinema history, which began in 1962.
Self, played by Daniel Craig.
Self, played by Pierce Brosnan.
Self, played by Timothy Dalton.
Self, played by Roger Moore.
Self, played by George Lazenby.
Self, played by Judi Dench.
James Bond 007: Everything or Nothing is a 2004 action adventure game developed by EA Redwood
Shores and published by Electronic Arts for the PlayStation 2, GameCube, and Xbox.
The game features a cast of voice actors including Pierce Brosnan,
reprising his film role as MI6 agent James Bond.
Other returning actors include Richard Kiel, John Cleese and Judi Dench, as Jaws, Q and M
respectively, alongside Willem Dafoe, Heidi Klum, Misaki Ito, Shannon Elizabeth, and Mýa.
It is considered a continuation of Die Another Day (2002), featuring Brosnan and
Cleese in their final performances as Bond and Q, respectively.
Development of the game began in 2001.
Written by Bruce Feirstein, Danny Bilson, and Paul De Meo, Everything or Nothing
centers around Bond dealing with the use of nanotechnology as terrorism.
The player controls Bond, and the game includes several driving levels.
It is the second Bond game played in third-person after Tomorrow Never Dies (1999),
and is the first Bond game to feature a two-player cooperative mode.
Everything or Nothing was released in February 2004.
It received "generally positive reviews" according to Metacritic.
The film explores themes of cinema on cinema, filmmaking,
retrospective, british secret service, documentary filmmaking.
The tone is uplifting and intense.